xbox360cheats.com 2018-06-06

# Xbox 360 Cheats Privacy Policy

## Xbox 360 Cheats privacy policy

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form, or make a comment on an article.

You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### Contact Form Submissions

If you choose to email us, we retain the email address provided and any other details provided by you in order to respond to you, should it be necessary. We do not use any information submitted via the contact form for marketing purposes.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. To improve our website and (we continually strive to improve our website and application offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  4. To attempt to show you advertisements that are most relevant or helpful to you

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

## Do we use cookies?

If you allow, yes (cookies are small files that a site, app or its respective service provider(s) transfer to your device's hard drive (if you allow) that enables the sites, apps or service providers systems to recognize your device and capture and remember certain information).

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and interaction, so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## How long we retain your data

If you email us, we may retain that email indefinitely.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you may request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You may also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

## Partners

Certain partners have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from our website users in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party offerings have separate and independent privacy policies. We have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked offerings. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site, and welcome any feedback about these offerings.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use aggregated information about your visits to this and other websites, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## European Union Citizens

This site is not targeted towards citizens of the European Union. If you visit or use this website in any way whatsoever, you are agreeing and confirming you are not a citizen of the European Union.

## Your Consent

By using our site you consent to our online privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on May 24, 2018.
